https://www.carbroker.com.au/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHome › About › Privacy Policy
Privacy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Carbroker.com.au. If you have any questions about our practices, please email information@carbroker.com.au.
Information Collection and Use
We will not sell, share rent or use information about our customers in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
When a customer makes a price inquiry, we collect and store address and email details of the customer. The purpose of storing customer details is so that we will know the location where the car should be delivered. We do not store credit card details. Credit card transactions are conducted via 128 bit encrypted using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer).
Cookies
A cookie is data stored on a computer user’s hard drive about their use of the computer. We use cookies to keep track of which customers have been referred by our affiliates. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information when making purchases through our network.
Log files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer our website, track customers’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. (An IP address is a numerical identifier for a computer that is connected to a TCP / IP network such as the Internet. An example is 144.155.34.245.)
Sharing data
We may share aggregated demographic information with car dealers and affiliates. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual. We will not share transaction data about any specific customer or affiliate.
We will share customer information with car dealer and vice versa only when the customer agrees to accept a quote and agrees for the dealer to have the information.
Online Partnerships
Please note that Carbroker.com.au is a broker and deals with many different dealers and affiliates. Our privacy statement applies only to our website and servers and not to those of our dealers and affiliates.
Security
We take every reasonable precaution to protect our users’ information. Sensitive information gathered via our servers is protected both online and offline. All transaction information and sensitive data is transmitted encrypted using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) an industry leading standard for transmitting data across networks. The servers on which we store data are in a secure hosting environment.
See what our customers say about carbroker.com.au
Kim Hunter5/05/2020
Carbroker.com.au
Our StockServices
Car BrokerCar Brokers In AustraliaProfessional AdviceCar Buying ServiceCar Broker FormSell OnlyFinanceTrade In FormCorporate CustomersCar InsuranceExtended WarrantyPaint Protection and Fabric ProtectionImmigrants/Expats Back
Information
Car Buying FAQSavingsThe CatchesImmigrants/ExpatsWhy is my trade in worth so little?CarsGuaranteeDealer InformationDealer LocationsCorporate Back
Research
Which New Car to Buy?New Car PricesCar News and ReviewsOptions and AccessoriesFleet PurchasesYour Trade inDealer TricksReverse Car Auctions Back
Finance
Car LoansNovated LeaseNovated Lease CalculatorCar Loans and LeasingCar Loans CalculatorRepayment Calculator Back
About
COVID-19 UpdatesReviewsContactHistoryPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsDispute ResolutionResponsible LendingFinancial Services Guide Back
× Close Panel
